Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1932-2004; XVIII.
  - Governor of Pennsylvania, 1979-1987; 9.
    - Ginny Thornburgh
      - PA Hospice Network Award Presentation (1), October, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 12)
      - Photograph of Ginny Thornburgh by Rosalinda R. Madara (1), October, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 13)
      - Easter Seal Society of Allegheny County, 50th Anniversary Dinner (2), October, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 14)
      - 1986 Farm Show (1), January, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 15)
      - Pine Creek Pete (1), February, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 16)
      - Montefiore Hospital (1), March 18, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 17)
      - Canterbury Place Groundbreaking (1), May 6, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 18)
      - Honorary Degrees awarded to Ginny Thornburgh: Dickinson School of Law (May 31, 1986), Duquesne University (May 8, 1987) (4), 1986, 1987 (Box 1523, Folder 19)
      - ARC of Chester County ADAPT Center (2), June 9, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 20)
      - 1986 Keystone State Games Torch Lighting (2), Summer, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 21)
      - Forbes Humanitarian Award (2), August, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 22)
      - Ginny Thornburgh Foundation (1), September, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 23)
      - Reservoir to River Run with Peter (1), September 19, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 24)
      - Hershey Park's 50th Anniversary (1), October 22, 1986 (Box 1523, Folder 25)
      - Gertrude Barber Center Visits, Erie, PA (9), Undated (Box 1523, Folder 26)
      - Ginny Thornburgh Under the Republican Umbrella (1), Undated (Box 1523, Folder 27)
      - McClure, Louise with Ginny Thornburgh (1), Undated (Box 1523, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous Ginny Thornburgh Photos, Undated (Box 1523, Folder 29)
    - Governor's Home
      - Governor's Home during the 1972 Flood, Harrisburg, PA (8) (Box 1523, Folder 30)
      - Exterior of Governor's Home, Harrisburg, PA (4), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 31)
      - The Entrance Hall (1), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 32)
      - Drawing Room (3), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 33)
      - Grand Hall (6), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 34)
      - State Rooms (3), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 35)
      - Library (3), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 36)
      - Family Living Room (8), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 37)
      - Family Dining Room (1), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 38)
      - Family Breakfast Room (1), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 39)
      - Porch (2), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 40)
      - 3rd Floor (1), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 41)
      - Gardens (5), 1980-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 42)
      - Gardens (2), Spring, 1980 (Box 1523, Folder 43)
      - Dedication of Governor's Homes Gardens (3), June 7, 1981 (Box 1523, Folder 44)
      - Governor and Ginny Thornburgh at Governor's Home (7), 1979-1986 (Box 1523, Folder 45)
      - Ginny and Peter Thornburgh at the Governor's Home, undated (Box 1523, Folder 46)
    - Formal Photographs of Dick and Ginny Thornburgh
      - Governor Dick Thornburgh, Formal Photographs (5), 1979-1986 (Box 1524, Folder 1)
      - Governor Dick Thornburgh, Informal Photographs (37), 1979-1986 (Box 1524, Folder 2 - 5)
      - Ginny Thornburgh, Professional Photographs (14), 1979-1986 (Box 1524, Folder 6)
      - Governor and Ginny Thornburgh, Formal Photographs (7), 1979-1986 (Box 1524, Folder 7)
      - Governor and Ginny Thornburgh, Informal Photographs (8), 1979-1986 (Box 1524, Folder 8)
    - Transition
      - Moving out of the Governor's Home, January 19, 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 9)
    - Legacy
      - Formal Photographs for Cover of Legacy and book Where the Evidence Leads, 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 10)
      - Photographs Used/Considered for Legacy, 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Politics, 1987-1988; 10.
    - Formal Photographs (3), 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 12)
    - Book of Proofs (22), 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 13)
    - Director, Institute of Politics (4), 1987-1988 (Box 1524, Folder 14)
    - John F. Kennedy, Jr. (1), 1987-1988 (Box 1524, Folder 15)
    - Meeting with Ted Kennedy (3), May 9, 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 16)
    - Peres, Shimon, Foreign Minister of Israel (3), September 21, 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 17)
    - National Press Club Press Conference regarding Balanced Budget, Washington, DC (1), December 3, 1987 (Box 1524, Folder 18)
    - Staff Photo (1), April 14, 1988 (Box 1524, Folder 19)
    - George Bush, Dick Thornburgh and PA Attorney General LeRoy Zimmerman, undated (Box 1524, Folder 20)
    - Endorsement for President George Bush, Lancaster, PA (2), April 20, 1988 (Box 1524, Folder 21)
    - GOP Reception with Elsie Hillman and Governor Kean of New Jersey (1), May 18, 1988 (Box 1524, Folder 22)
    - York College Commencement (1), May 14, 1988 (Box 1524, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Institute of Politics Photograph, including University of Pittsburgh School of Law Medallion of Distinction award with Mark Nordenberg and others, February 23, 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 1524, Folder 24)
    - University of Pittsburgh Masoner Lecture, and School of Law Medallion of Distinction, 1988 (Box 1524, Folder 25)
    - Suffolk School of Law Graduation, June 5, 1988 (Box 1524, Folder 26)
  - Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; 11.
    - Official Attorney General of the United States Photograph Albums
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (67), July-December, 1988 (Box 1525, Folder 1)
      - In front of Supreme Court after arguing Burnley vs Railway Labor Executives, November 2, 1988 (Box 1525, Folder 2)
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (84), January-June, 1989 (Box 1526, Folder 1)
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (84), July-December, 1989 (Box 1526, Folder 2)
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (111), January-June, 1990 (Box 1527, Folder 1)
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (102), July-December, 1990 (Box 1527, Folder 2)
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (137), January-April, 1991 (Box 1528, Folder 1)
      - Attorney General of the United States Photograph Album (107), May-August, 1991 (Box 1528, Folder 2)
    - Events and People
      - ABA-Federal Legal Executives Forum Luncheon (5), June 29, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 1)
      - ABA-Soviet Lawyer Internship Project (1), September 21, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 2)
      - Abell, Rick (OJP) Farewell Ceremony (2), August 2, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 3)
      - Abraham, Lynne, District Attorney of Philadelphia (1), June 24, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 4)
      - Abshire, David, President of the Center for Strategic and International Studies (1), January 4, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 5)
      - Alexander, Lamar--Reception (3), April 16, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 6)
      - American Law Institute--Luncheon (5), May 19, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 7)
      - Announcement of Thornburgh as Attorney General of the United States, July 11, 1988 (Box 1529, Folder 8)
      - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith--Meeting with David Brody (1), July 31, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 9)
      - Anti-Trust Division--Brown Bag Lunch (3), January 12, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 10)
      - Anti-Trust Division--Coffee (2), January 30, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 11)
      - Ashcroft, John, Governor of Missouri (2), February 20, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 12)
      - Asian-American Delegation--Family Reunification (4), July 18, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 13)
      - Association for Retarded Citizens--Annual Convention in Tampa, FL (3), November 8, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 14)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys (2), December 16, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 15)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys (2), March 14, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 16)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys (1), May 22, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 17)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys (2), May 23, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 18)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys (2), March 13, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 19)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys (2), Undated (Box 1529, Folder 20)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys--Interview with Nancy Allen on AGAC History (1), December 20, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 21)
      - Attorney General's Awards Ceremony (3), January 26, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 22)
      - Attorney General's Birthday Party (5), July 16, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 23)
      - Attorney General's Birthday Party (6), July 16, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 24)
      - Attorney General's Birthday Party (6), July 16, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 25)
      - Attorney General's Office Staff (3), Undated (Box 1529, Folder 26)
      - Attorney General's Speech to Department of Justice Employees (6), October 17, 1988 (Box 1529, Folder 27)
      - Attorney General's Swearing In Ceremony and official Attorney General photographs and negatives, August 12, 1988 (Box 1529, Folder 28)
      - Baker, Susan (wife of James Baker, Secretary of State) and Clement Conger, Curator of State Rooms (1), undated (Box 1529, Folder 29)
      - Barlas, Jimmy, Barber at National Press Building Barbershop, Fall, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 30)
      - Barr, Bill, Surprise 40th Birthday Party (2), May 23, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 31)
      - Barnett, Hank, Chairman of Bethlehem Steel (2), May 31, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 32)
      - Bohlmann, Dr. Ralph, Lutheran Church (2), August 14, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 33)
      - Boston Center for Independent Living (8), September 14, 1989 (Box 1529, Folder 34)
      - Boys Clubs of America, Board of Directors (4), September 26, 1988 (Box 1529, Folder 35)
      - Brauer, Mary Lou (1), August 3, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 36)
      - Bravo, Ken (1), June 17, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 37)
      - Breeden, Richard, SEC Chairman (2), May 29, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 38)
      - Brill, Gerilyn and Gale McKenzie (2), February 28, 1991 (Box 1529, Folder 39)
      - Budget Reform Package (2), April 24, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 40)
      - Burke, James of Partnership for a Drug Free America (3), January 4, 1990 (Box 1529, Folder 41)
      - Burroughs, David, Summer Staff Assistant for the Office of the Attorney General (1), undated (Box 1529, Folder 42)
      - Bush, Barbara with Ginny Thornburgh (3), 1989-1991 (Box 1529, Folder 43)
      - Bush Cabinet Photos (2), 1988-1991 (Box 1530, Folder 1)
      - Bush Christmas Party Photographs (3), 1988-1991 (Box 1530, Folder 2)
      - Bush, President George, Remarks to Conestoga Valley High School, Lancaster County, PA (2), March 22, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 3)
      - Bush, President George, Informal Working Photos (6), 1990-1991 (Box 1530, Folder 4)
      - Bush, President George with Ginny Thornburgh (2), 1990-1991 (Box 1530, Folder 5)
      - Butler, Michael, undated (Box 1530, Folder 6)
      - Cabinet Wives and Barbara Bush (3), 1989-1990 (Box 1530, Folder 7)
      - Campanelli, Richard (2), undated (Box 1530, Folder 8)
      - Campion, Heather and John Howe of the Institute of Politics (2), February 22, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 9)
      - Cartusciello, Neil and John Cruden of the ENR Division (1), May 14, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 10)
      - Carvino, Jim (1), undated (Box 1530, Folder 11)
      - Cassalia, Maria and Dr. Peter (2), November 18, 1988 (Box 1530, Folder 12)
      - Christman, Dan (2), undated (Box 1530, Folder 13)
      - City Club Forum Luncheon, Cleveland, OH, May 11, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 14)
      - Civil Division--Brown Bag Lunch (2), January 30, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 15)
      - Civil Division--Brown Bag Lunch (2), September 27, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 16)
      - Civil Division--Coffee (3), January 29, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 17)
      - Civil Division Roundtable (2), January 30, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 18)
      - Civil Division--Coffee (2), May 8, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 19)
      - Civil Rights Division--Coffee (2), October 10, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 20)
      - Civil Rights Division--Brown Bag Lunch (3), February 14, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 21)
      - Clements, Bill, Governor of Texas (1), February 27, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 22)
      - Coalitions for America--721 Group (1), July 30, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 23)
      - Coalition for Women's Appointments (3), June 29, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 24)
      - Cochran, Jan (1), January 5, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 25)
      - Cole, Charles, AG of Alaska (2), January 28, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 26)
      - Collins, Marvin, U.S. Attorney of Fort Worth (4), July 11, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 27)
      - Community Relations Service (20), March 28, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 28)
      - Conference of Chief Justices with Justice Carricio (2), May 23, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 29)
      - Coro Foundation Fellows, Meeting (3), July 12, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 30)
      - Crawford, Carol, Swearing-In Ceremony (6), June 1, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 31)
      - Crime Bill Meeting with NAAG and NDAA (6), September 12, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 32)
      - Criminal Division--Brown Bag Lunch (4), January 5, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 33)
      - Criminal Division--Coffee (3), January 10, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 34)
      - Criminal Division--Coffee (3), April 11, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 35)
      - Crossley, Norma, Deputy Attorney General's Office (1), undated (Box 1530, Folder 36)
      - Crowe, Admiral William (2), January 8, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 37)
      - Damon, James National President of the Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks (3), September 25, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 38)
      - Dart, Justin (3), July 27, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 39)
      - Dechant, Virgil, Knights of Columbus (1), July 12, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 40)
      - Dennis, Dick (OIA) and Adam Dennis (1), March 8, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 41)
      - Dennis, Ed, AAG--Criminal Division, Farwell Reception (2), July 31, 1990 (Box 1530, Folder 42)
      - Deputy Attorney General's Office--Brown Bag Lunch (2), January 24, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 43)
      - Derwinski, Edward, Secretary of Veterans Affairs (2), May 26, 1989 (Box 1530, Folder 44)
      - DeWitt, Chuck, Presentation of Presidential Commission (1), June 11, 1991 (Box 1530, Folder 45)
      - Dilbert Rosalie, 1990 Clarissa Hughes Teacher of the Year Award Winner with Family (2), October 1, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 1)
      - Dobson, Dr. James, "Focus on the Family" (2), April 11, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 2)
      - Department of Justice Child Development Center (2), July 29, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 3)
      - DOJ Command Center (1), November 28, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 4)
      - DOJ Command Center Staff, Bill Jasnowski and John Hutchins, February 2, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 5)
      - DOJ Command Center, Presentation of Plaque (1), January 10, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 6)
      - DOJ Component Heads Meeting (4), December 1, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 7)
      - DOJ Component Heads Meeting (3), October 5, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 8)
      - DOJ Recreation Association (5), October 14, 1988 (Box 1531, Folder 9)
      - DOJ Summer Law Interns (2), August 1, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 10)
      - DOJ Volunteers (4), April 20, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 11)
      - Drug Enforcement Administration Memorial Service, Annual Event (4), May 29, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 12)
      - Drug Enforcement Administration Headquarters Dedication Ceremony, Arlington, VA (11), October 13, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 13)
      - Drug Enforcement Administration--Brown Bag Lunch (4), February 23, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 14)
      - Drug Enforcement Administration--Brown Bag Lunch (2), May 13, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 15)
      - Drug Free School Recognition Program, Rose Garden (1), June 7, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 16)
      - Duffy, John, Sheriff of San Diego County, CA (1), April 4, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 17)
      - Dunne, John, Swearing-in Ceremony (7), April 17, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 18)
      - Durren, Scott (2), December 11, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 19)
      - Earth Day Ceremony (7), April 24, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 20)
      - Elks (2), September 19, 1988 (Box 1531, Folder 21)
      - Enhanced Recision Announcement (1), August 4, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 22)
      - ENR Division--Brown Bag Lunch (3), January 10, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 23)
      - ENR Division--Coffee (3), January 23, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 24)
      - EOUSA--Awards Ceremony (1), October 20, 1988 (Box 1531, Folder 25)
      - EOUSA--Brown Bag Lunch (2), March 16, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 26)
      - Executive Staff (DOJ) and Spouses (12), November 14, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 27)
      - Family Research Council (4), October 18, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 28)
      - Federalist Society (1), November 19, 1990 OR November 30, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 29)
      - Federal Bar Association--Tom Clark Award (3), August 25, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 30)
      - FBI Detail: Tracy, Oller, and Ragle (3), April 5, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 31)
      - FBI Medal of Valor Ceremony (8), April 10, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 32)
      - FBI Social Events (2), 1988-1991 (Box 1531, Folder 33)
      - FBI Special Agent Memorial Service (8), November 14, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 34)
      - Federal Judges Association (14), May 24, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 35)
      - Federal Law Enforcement Agencies Luncheon (2), May 21, 1990 (Box 1531, Folder 36)
      - Ferazzi, Keith (1), Undated (Box 1531, Folder 37)
      - Fisher, PA Senator Mike and PA Senator Frank Pecora (1), January 30, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 38)
      - Fraternal Order of the Police, Pittsburgh, PA, August 14, 1991 (Box 1531, Folder 39)
      - Gage, Nicholas of Paramount Pictures (1), January 13, 1989 (Box 1531, Folder 40)
      - Gerson, Stuart, Swearing-In Ceremony (1), January 3, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 1)
      - Giamatti, Bartlett Baseball Commissioner (1), August 3, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 2)
      - Giavia, Alexandra (3), April 16, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 3)
      - Gleason, Rob and Jeanne (2), February 8, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 4)
      - Goldberg, Judge Dick (1), May 21, 1991 (Box 1532, Folder 5)
      - Goldberg, Fred, Commissioner of the IRS (1), April 10, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 6)
      - Grant, Marcia (1), February 7, 1991 (Box 1532, Folder 7)
      - Gruber, Charles, President of IACP (3), May 15, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 8)
      - Governor Portrait Unveiling (6), January 11, 1991 (Box 1532, Folder 9)
      - Haller, Dr. Joe, Rocco Scalzi, and Jeff Shoaf (1), November 3, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 10)
      - Hankinson, Richard--Swearing In Ceremony (3), July 31, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 11)
      - Henderson, Doug (1)`, November 3, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 12)
      - Hermoza, Yliana, Former KSG Student (1), February 5, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 13)
      - Hillsborough County Bar Association, Tampa (3), November 8, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 14)
      - Hispanic American Police Command Officers Association (1), March 30, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 15)
      - Hispanic National Bar Association (1), July 9, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 16)
      - Hoeveler, Jinny and Ann Thornburgh (1), July 18, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 17)
      - Holiday, Ede, White House Cabinet Secretary (1), July 5, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 18)
      - Howard, John--Farewell Reception (2), July 12, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 19)
      - Hubbard, Alan, E.D. of the Council on Competitiveness (3), July 19, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 20)
      - Hughes, Richard (1), February 2, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 21)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service--Brown Bag Lunch (2), March 14, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 22)
      - Immigration Bill--White House Ceremony (1), November 29, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 23)
      - International Club #1 (1), September 26, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 24)
      - Italian-American Working Group (7), April 4, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 25)
      - Jackson, Michael (1), September 13, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 26)
      - Jackson, Reverend Jesse (2), August 21, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 27)
      - Jackson, William (1), December 15, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 28)
      - Japanese-American Redress Check Presentation (2), October 9, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 29)
      - Justice Management Division--Brown Bag Lunch (22), February 5, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 30)
      - Keating, Frank (1), September 30, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 31)
      - Kemp, Jack, Secretary of HUD (2), March 17, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 32)
      - Kennedy School of Government, Summer in Washington Program Interns (1), July 5, 1990 (Box 1532, Folder 33)
      - King, Dr. Martin Luther--Commemoration (20), January 16, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 34)
      - King, Tom (1), August 18, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 35)
      - Kirk, Dr. Jerry, Chairman of Religious Alliance Against Pornography (2), October 27, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 36)
      - Kirkpatrick, Jamie (1), December 21, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 37)
      - Kmiec, Doug (3), June 20, 1989 (Box 1532, Folder 38)
      - Korten, Pat--Farewell Party (3), October 4, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 39)
      - Kourakos, Stella, DOJ Employee (3), October 19, 1988 (Box 1532, Folder 40)
      - Larson, Tom--Swearing In Ceremony (1), March 20, 1991 (Box 1533, Folder 1)
      - Law Enforcement Officers Memorial (6), October 30, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 2)
      - Law Enforcement Steering Committee Meeting (2), November 4, 1988 (Box 1533, Folder 3)
      - Law Enforcement Steering Committee Meeting (4), undated (Box 1533, Folder 4)
      - Lawn, Jack, Administrator of DEA (1), September 9, 1988 (Box 1533, Folder 5)
      - Lawn, Jack, Administrator of DEA--Farewell Reception and Dinner (3), March 20, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 6)
      - Lay, Chief Judge Donald of the 8th Circuit (2), February 20, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 7)
      - "Legal Advocates in Education" Program at Stuart Hobson Middle School, Washington, DC (7), May 24, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 8)
      - "Legal Advocates in Education" Program at Stuart Hobson Middle School, Washington, DC (2), October 4, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 9)
      - Lincoln Legal Foundation (8), August 20, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 10)
      - Los Angeles Mayor's Alliance for a Drug-Free Community (2), September 25, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 11)
      - Lungren, Dan, Former CA congressman (2), January 18, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 12)
      - Luttig, Mike (1), January 25, 1991 (Box 1533, Folder 13)
      - MacCormack, Cam (1), undated (Box 1533, Folder 14)
      - Mahoney, Maureen, Deputy Solicitor General (2), July 2, 1991 (Box 1533, Folder 15)
      - Maloney, Andrew, U.S. Attorney from Brooklyn (1), undated (Box 1533, Folder 16)
      - Markman, Steve--Farewell Reception (1), undated (Box 1533, Folder 17)
      - Martoche, Salvator (2), October 13, 1988 (Box 1533, Folder 18)
      - Marzulla, Roger, AAG, Lands Division (1), January 18, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 19)
      - Matthews, Ardre (1), May 29, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 20)
      - Medrano, Manuel and John Carlton, U.S. Attorneys from Los Angeles (1), September 13, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 21)
      - Meese Portrait Unveiling (3), July 25, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 22)
      - Moore, Mike, Director of U.S. Marshals Service--Swearing In Ceremony (2), December 6, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 23)
      - Mueller, Robert S. III--Presentation of Presidential Commission (2), January 22, 1991 (Box 1533, Folder 24)
      - Mueller, Robert S. III (1), March 1, 1991 (Box 1533, Folder 25)
      - McKay, Mike, USA of Seattle, WA and AUSAs (14), March 21, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 26)
      - McMunn, David and Richard Porter (2), November 7, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 27)
      - McNary, Gene, INS--Swearing In Ceremony (7), November 16, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 28)
      - National Association of Attorneys General (29), March 11, 1991 (Box 1533, Folder 29)
      - National Association of Attorneys General, Antitrust Working Group (2), October 19, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 30)
      - National Association of Counties--Executive Committee (1), September 7, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 31)
      - National Conference on State and Local Drug Policy (7), May 15, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 32)